{"content":[{"id":"328c8a95","settings":{"height":"min-height","custom_height":{"unit":"px","size":"","sizes":[]},"content_position":"middle","background_background":"classic","background_repeat":"no-repeat","background_size":"cover","background_overlay_background":"classic","background_overlay_opacity":{"unit":"px","size":0.8,"sizes":[]},"margin":{"unit":"px","top":"","right":0,"bottom":"","left":0,"isLinked":true},"padding":{"unit":"px","top":"100","right":"0","bottom":"80","left":"0","isLinked":false},"background_color":"#151414","background_color_b":"#8857EB","background_color_b_stop":{"unit":"%","size":60,"sizes":[]},"background_gradient_angle":{"unit":"deg","size":280,"sizes":[]},"padding_mobile":{"unit":"px","top":"50","right":"20","bottom":"50","left":"20","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"5676bb2"}],"padding_tablet":{"unit":"px","top":"50","right":"20","bottom":"50","left":"20","isLinked":false}},"elements":[{"id":"643d1e91","settings":{"_column_size":100,"_inline_size":null,"content_position":"center","align":"center","padding":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"15ab361"}]},"elements":[{"id":"4304f702","settings":{"structure":"40","border_width":{"unit":"px","top":"1","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":false},"border_color":"#E1E1E1","_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"f47a092"}]},"elements":[{"id":"53ab2a02","settings":{"_column_size":25,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":33,"margin_mobile":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"30","left":"0","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"e305df8"}]},"elements":[{"id":"6c549e","settings":{"title":"Shop","title_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":18,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"50ecbd7"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"heading","elType":"widget"},{"id":"6fea5639","settings":{"editor":"31 Southlands Road <br>\nPOLESWORTH <br>\nB78 0FL","align_mobile":"left","text_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":14,"sizes":[]},"typography_line_height":{"unit":"em","size":1.7,"sizes":[]},"_margin":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":true},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"77d7473"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"text-editor","elType":"widget"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"},{"id":"1e89c896","settings":{"_column_size":25,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":35,"margin_mobile":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"30","left":"0","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"65eb6cb"}]},"elements":[{"id":"22f36ccc","settings":{"title":"Contact","title_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":18,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"4b9229b"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"heading","elType":"widget"},{"id":"3d247afc","settings":{"icon_list":[{"text":"Contact@happyaddons.com","selected_icon":{"value":"hm hm-mail-open","library":"happy-icons"},"_id":"19bc6c4"},{"text":"0123 22123 2323","selected_icon":{"value":"hm hm-headphone","library":"happy-icons"},"_id":"100a228"}],"space_between":{"unit":"px","size":14,"sizes":[]},"icon_color":"#FFFFFF","icon_size":{"unit":"px","size":20,"sizes":[]},"text_color":"#FFFFFF","text_indent":{"unit":"px","size":19,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"7409b1b"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"icon-list","elType":"widget"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"},{"id":"2890989c","settings":{"_column_size":25,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":31,"margin_mobile":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"30","left":"0","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"6fea857"}]},"elements":[{"id":"7f4796d9","settings":{"title":"Quick Links","title_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":18,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"cb45f9b"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"heading","elType":"widget"},{"id":"227a2de9","settings":{"icon_list":[{"text":"About Us","selected_icon":{"value":"","library":""},"_id":"1651664","link":{"url":"#","is_external":"","nofollow":"","custom_attributes":""}},{"text":"Contact Us","selected_icon":{"value":"","library":""},"link":{"url":"#","is_external":"","nofollow":"","custom_attributes":""},"_id":"d038f3a"},{"text":"Privacy Policy","selected_icon":{"value":"","library":""},"link":{"url":"#","is_external":"","nofollow":"","custom_attributes":""},"_id":"d35c86d"}],"space_between":{"unit":"px","size":15,"sizes":[]},"space_between_mobile":{"unit":"px","size":25,"sizes":[]},"icon_align":"left","icon_align_mobile":"left","icon_self_align":"left","text_color":"#FFFFFF","text_color_hover":"#FDD247","text_indent":{"unit":"px","size":0,"sizes":[]},"icon_typography_typography":"custom","icon_typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":14,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"1d82a36"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"icon-list","elType":"widget"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"},{"id":"76fd500e","settings":{"_column_size":25,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":70,"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"598f468"}]},"elements":[{"id":"37a5470c","settings":{"title":"Social","title_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":18,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"259d54a"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"heading","elType":"widget"},{"id":"7223d762","settings":{"social_icon_list":[{"social_icon":{"value":"fab fa-facebook","library":"fa-brands"},"_id":"ae880e4"},{"social_icon":{"value":"fab fa-twitter","library":"fa-brands"},"_id":"47850e1"},{"social_icon":{"value":"fab fa-youtube","library":"fa-brands"},"_id":"6093371"}],"shape":"circle","align":"left","icon_size":{"unit":"px","size":18,"sizes":[]},"icon_spacing":{"unit":"px","size":15,"sizes":[]},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"3a505ae"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"social-icons","elType":"widget"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"section"},{"id":"1a268920","settings":{"content_position":"middle","structure":"20","border_width":{"unit":"px","top":"1","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":false},"border_color":"#E1E1E1","padding":{"unit":"px","top":"50","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":false},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"d4ec478"}],"padding_mobile":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":false}},"elements":[{"id":"5974aa57","settings":{"_column_size":50,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":30,"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"360da61"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"},{"id":"4c3e3632","settings":{"_column_size":50,"_inline_size":null,"_inline_size_tablet":70,"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"c8509df"}]},"elements":[{"id":"4d359e9a","settings":{"editor":"<p>\u00a9 Copyright 2019 HappyAddons. All right reserved.<\/p>","align":"right","align_mobile":"center","text_color":"#FFFFFF","typography_typography":"custom","typography_font_size":{"unit":"px","size":14,"sizes":[]},"_margin":{"unit":"px","top":"0","right":"0","bottom":"0","left":"0","isLinked":true},"_ha_condition_list":[{"_ha_condition_key":"login_status","_ha_condition_operator":"is","_ha_condition_login_status":"login","_ha_condition_role":"subscriber","_ha_condition_operating_system":"mac_os","_ha_condition_browser":"chrome","_ha_condition_date_range":"19-05-2020 to 21-05-2020","_ha_condition_date":"19-05-2020","_ha_condition_time":"12:00","_ha_condition_day":"monday","_id":"ca45506"}]},"elements":[],"isInner":false,"widgetType":"text-editor","elType":"widget"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"column"}],"isInner":true,"elType":"section"}],"isInner":false,"elType":"column"}],"isInner":false,"elType":"section"}],"page_settings":{"ha_grid_zindex":"1000","eael_ext_toc_title":"Table of Contents"},"version":"0.4","title":"footer","type":"section"}